[music]
[音乐]
Hello and welcome to section five
您好，欢迎来到第五节
of lesson one.
第一课
Here we're going to talk about method and constructor references,
在这里，我们将讨论方法和构造函数引用，
which are shorthand forms of defining
这是定义的简写形式
certain types of Lambda expressions. Often
某些类型的Lambda表达式。经常
the kind of Lambda expression that we end up with is a very simple
我们最终得到的那种Lambda表达式非常简单
kind of expression where all we’re doing is passing a parameter, in this case a
一种表达式，我们要做的就是传递一个参数，在这种情况下，
file, f, and the body of the Lambda expression simply calls a method
文件f和Lambda表达式的主体只是调用一个方法
on that parameter. In this case we call canRead
在该参数上。在这种情况下，我们称为canRead
on f. So, we've provided a
在f。因此，我们提供了一个
shorthand way of representing that which is
表示是的简写方式
a method reference. We can do the same thing by saying
方法参考。我们可以通过说同样的事情
file, which is just the type of the parameter, f,
文件，它只是参数f的类型，
colon colon, canRead,
冒号，可以读取，
which is the method that we want call on that particular
我们要在特定位置调用的方法
parameter, so we want to call f.canRead.
参数，所以我们要调用f.canRead。
The compiler will simply take that message reference
编译器将简单地获取该消息参考
and expand it into the above Lambda expression
并将其扩展为上述Lambda表达式
and then compile it in the same way. Now
然后以相同的方式进行编译。现在
there are some details about method references that we need to
我们需要一些有关方法引用的细节
understand because there are effectively three types,
了解，因为实际上有三种类型，
or three places where you can use method references and they vary
或三个可以使用方法引用的地方，它们会有所不同
slightly
略
in terms of the way that syntax works.
就语法的工作方式而言。
The three types are static methods,
这三种类型是静态方法，
where you have an instance method of
你有一个实例方法
an arbitrary type, so that’s one you're not referring to in terms of variable that
任意类型，因此您不是要使用的变量类型
you have in your code and then the third form is an
您已经在代码中，然后第三种形式是
instance method on an existing object
现有对象上的实例方法
which is a variable that you have in your code where you want to call a
这是您在代码中要调用的变量
method
方法
on that. The the format of
在那。格式
the method reference as it shows here is that you have your target reference,
此处显示的方法参考是您拥有目标参考，
that’s your reference
那是你的参考
type colon colon and then the name of the method
键入冒号冒号，然后输入方法的名称
that is going to be called through that method reference.
将通过该方法引用进行调用。
In terms of how we construct those,
关于我们如何构造它们，
the rules vary a little bit, primarily in terms of when you have an
规则略有不同，主要取决于您何时拥有
instance of
的实例
an arbitrary type. For a static method
任意类型。对于静态方法
it's quite straightforward. If the Lambda expression is where you have a set of
这很简单。如果Lambda表达式是您拥有一组
arguments on the left hand side of the
左手边的参数
Lambda operator and then you're calling a static method on a particular
Lambda运算符，然后您在特定对象上调用静态方法
class with those arguments then
然后用这些参数上课
the equivalent method reference is simply the name
等效的方法引用只是名称
of that class and the name of the static method.
该类的名称以及静态方法的名称。
It’s very straightforward if you’re going to call, like integer.parseint
如果要拨打电话，这非常简单，例如integer.parseint
on a string then it's just integer colon colon parseint
在字符串上，那么它只是整数冒号冒号parseint
because that's the method that you calling on the the particular class.
因为那是您在特定类上调用的方法。
Where you're using an instance
您在哪里使用实例
of an arbitrary type which is one you don't already have a reference to,
是您还没有引用的任意类型的
it is slightly different in the way that
它在方式上略有不同
the parameters are used
使用参数
in terms of converting to a method reference.
在转换为方法参考方面。
In this example what we've got is argument zero
在此示例中，我们得到的参数为零
and then we’ve got some other arguments. In Lambda expression what we do is we use
然后我们还有其他一些争论。在Lambda表达式中，我们要做的是使用
the first argument
第一个论点
as the parameter that we want to call the method
作为我们要调用方法的参数
on and then we call the instance
然后我们调用实例方法
on that parameter and  we pass the rest of the parameters
在该参数上，我们传递其余参数
as arguments to that method. For that case
作为该方法的参数。对于那种情况
what we do is use the type of argument zero
我们要做的就是使用参数零的类型
as the class name colon colon and then
作为类名冒号冒号，然后
the same instance method name as we're calling the method
与我们调用该方法相同的实例方法名称
on that in our method reference. For
在我们的方法参考中。对于
a Lambda where we have a reference to
我们参考的Lambda
an existing variable where we want to use that in our
现有变量，我们希望在我们的变量中使用它
code again we’ll have a set of arguments on the left hand side,
再次编写代码，我们将在左侧有一组参数，
the right hand side of the Lambda expression will be a reference
Lambda表达式的右侧将作为参考
to a variable that we have in our code and a method that we want call on that.
到我们在代码中具有的变量以及要在其上调用的方法。
Then we'll be passing the arguments as parameters to that method.
然后，我们将参数作为参数传递给该方法。
The equivalent method reference is rather than using the type
等效的方法引用不是使用类型
of the class, the type of the
类的类型
the expression we use the expression itself
表达式我们使用表达式本身
and the compiler will understand what that type is for us
编译器将了解该类型对我们而言
and convert it into the appropriate Lambda expression above.
并将其转换为上面合适的Lambda表达式。
if we look at some examples of that,
如果我们看一些例子，
for a static method in this case what we’re doing is passing
对于这种情况下的静态方法，我们正在通过
string s and we want to print that string, so we have
string，我们想打印该字符串，所以我们有
System.out.println of s. The equivalent method reference
的System.out.println等效方法参考
is simply to say System.out
只是说System.out
which is the class
这是班
that we want to use and println is the static method
我们要使用的方法和println是静态方法
of that class. In that case
该类的。在这种情况下
s will be passed as a parameter. Where we have
s将作为参数传递。我们在哪里
a reference to a type that we don't have
对我们没有的类型的引用
in our class, so this is an arbitrary type.
在我们的课上，所以这是一个任意类型。
In this case what we have is string s
在这种情况下，我们拥有的是字符串s
and int i and we’re calling substring on the
和诠释我，我们在
variable s with
变量s
the parameter i. The conversion there,
参数i。那里的转换，
as I said on the previous slide is that we use the type
正如我在上一张幻灯片中说的那样，我们使用
of s, string, don’t need to use s, we just use the type
的s，字符串，不需要使用s，我们只使用类型
string and the reference to the method that we want to call substring.
字符串以及对我们要调用子字符串的方法的引用。
Again the compiler will figure out that,
再次，编译器会发现，
in that case, we don’t need to
在这种情况下，我们不需要
pass s as a parameter, we’re only using the
将s作为参数传递，我们仅使用
i parameter as a parameter to substring. Then the last form where we’re referring to
我将参数作为子字符串的参数。然后是我们指的最后一个表格
something that we already have a reference to
我们已经参考过的东西
in this case what we've got is axis a
在这种情况下，我们得到的是轴a
as the parameter and then we’re calling getLength
作为参数，然后我们调用getLength
on a, where getLength is a method that exists
在a上，其中getLength是存在的方法
in the class that we’re actually executing our code in.
在我们实际执行代码的类中。
In this case, rather than referring to the type of the class
在这种情况下，而不是引用类的类型
we use a reference to this, because this refers to the object that we’re in
我们使用对此的引用，因为这引用了我们所在的对象
and then we call getLength on that because getLength is the method
然后我们就调用getLength，因为getLength是方法
in that current object and the parameter is
在当前对象中，参数为
a, and that will automatically be passed to getLength. We can use the same
a，它将自动传递给getLength。我们可以使用相同的
idea for a constructor reference, because
构造函数参考的想法，因为
a constructor is very much like a method takes parameters
构造函数非常像方法需要参数
and creates a new object. What we have here is an example where
并创建一个新对象。我们这里有一个例子
we've got a factory that wants to create lists of type string.
我们有一家工厂想要创建字符串类型的列表。
We have a lambda expression which is in effect a
我们有一个lambda表达式，实际上
supplier, which will take no arguments
供应商，这不会引起任何争论
and will return new ArrayList of type string. We can
并将返回字符串类型的新ArrayList。我们可以
use the equivalent shortcut that we have for the method reference,
使用我们为方法参考使用的等效快捷方式，
but as a constructor reference. Rather than calling a specific method
但作为构造函数参考。而不是调用特定方法
we want to instantiate a new object so we just use
我们想实例化一个新对象，所以我们只使用
new. We have ArrayList&lt;String&gt; colon colon
新。我们有ArrayList &lt;String&gt;冒号
new to indicate that we're going to create a new instance ArrayList
new表示我们将创建一个新实例ArrayList
of type string. To summarize section
字符串类型。总结部分
five what method references do
五方法引用做什么
is give us a shorthand notation for a lot of
给我们很多的简写
common simple Lambdas.
常见的简单Lambda。
What you'll find is as you start to use them more and more,
当您开始越来越多地使用它们时，您会发现，
they will become much easier to read and you’ll understand what's actually happening
它们将变得更容易阅读，您将了解实际情况
in the code much more easily.
在代码中更容易。
There are three different types and
有三种不同的类型和
how we use them depends on what the format is and remember that
我们如何使用它们取决于格式，请记住
if you’re using an arbitrary type the way that the parameters are processed is that the first
如果您使用的是任意类型，则参数的处理方式是：
parameter is used
使用参数
as the type of the thing that you want to call the method on
作为您要在其上调用方法的事物的类型
and the rest of the parameters are passed as arguments to that method.
其余参数作为参数传递给该方法。
We can use the same thing with a constructor so we can have a constructor reference
我们可以对构造函数使用相同的东西，所以我们可以有一个构造函数引用
rather than calling a particular method
而不是调用特定方法
we use the reference to new rather than the method name
我们使用对new的引用而不是方法名
And that is the end of this part
到此为止
of the lesson.
本课。